<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<news> xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
    xsi:schemalocation="schema.xsd">
  <entry date="24.05.2024">
	<headline>Gasly to miss crucial laps with issue in Monaco.</headline>
	<body>Not the way Pierre Gasly wanted to start this weekend in Monaco. In FP1, the Frenchman was already called into the pit lane as he was told his car has a power unit issue. Gasly was then let out to test his car again, but Alpine quickly called him back as the issue did not go away quickly.</body>
	<by>Kada Sarkozi</by>
	<source>https://www.gpblog.com/en/news/278210/painful-moment-for-alpine-gasly-to-miss-crucial-laps-with-issue-in-monaco.html</source>
  </entry>
  <entry date="20.05.2024">
	<headline>Esteban Ocon and Haas begin negotiations.</headline>
	<body>Esteban Ocon is emerging as an increasingly central player in the driver market. He is understood to have begun contract talks with Haas as he evaluates the different options for 2025. With his existing Alpine contract expiring this year, the Frenchman faces some big decisions.</body>
	<by>Jaden Diaz</by>
	<source>https://formu1a.uno/en/esteban-ocon-enters-negotiations-with-haas/</source>
  </entry>
  <entry date="10.05.2024">
	<headline>Aerodynamics specialist leaves Red Bull Racing for top job at Alpine.</headline>
	<body>Alpine have completed another signing technical team. Michael Broadhurst makes the move to the French racing stable and will work alongside David Sanchez, as will join the French team from Red Bull Racing.</body>
	<by>Tim Kraiiji</by>
	<source>https://www.gpblog.com/en/news/275398/red-bull-loses-technical-leader-to-alpine.html</source>
  </entry>
    <entry date="02.05.2024">
	<headline>Sanchez joins Alpine as F1 technical director.</headline>
	<body>Ex-Ferrari engineer David Sanchez has joined Alpine's Formula 1 team as executive technical director, following his departure from McLaren after just three months in his role.</body>
	<by>Jake Boxall-Legge</by>
	<source>https://www.motorsport.com/f1/news/sanchez-joins-alpine-as-f1-technical-director-after-mclaren-exit/10605595/</source>
  </entry>
</news> 